HANS VEITIA

Appian | Help Desk | Tech Recruitment



Summary

IT professional with 4 years in the industry, with background in help desk and IT support services, more recently focused in Appian development, with 1 year hands on experience on solution support, as well as in development and quality assurance responsibilities at a high-paced app development environment at an oil refinery in the US.

Experience

- Appian Jr Developer / Solution Support (2021-present)
 - o USA
 - o Thailand
- Tech Recruitment IT Interviews Manager (2020-present)
 - o Brazil
- Help Desk Support Agent (2018-2020)
 - o Brazil

Skill Highlights

- Debugging & hot fix
- UI development
- Process & Function development
- Quality assurance
- ETL & data integration
- Document management

Recent Projects

Solution Support & Help Desk - Support Agent

Oil & Gas Refinery, United States

Responsible for supporting all apps in the Appian environment:

- Daily monitoring rounds
- Attend bugs reported
- Participate in enhancement implementation
- Proactive optimization derived from weekly health check reports

Vehicle Access Management – Jr. Developer / Tester

Energy Corporation, United States

Suite to enable employees and external contractors to submit ahead of time their vehicle pass to access the plant. The app allows for attachment upload, verification of insurance documentation and a multi-level approval workflow with additional dashboards for KPI monitoring and a separate administration site.

Contractor Work Management – Jr. Developer / Tester

Oil & Gas Refinery, United States

Suite for contractor representatives to submit access requests, those are then reviewed and approved by the respective area managers and subsequently sent over to the security/badge system for issuing or extension of access badges for contractors to be able to access the plant.

Project Portfolio Management – Jr. Developer / Tester

Energy Corporation, United States

Suite created for Operations to manage their projects through a robust workflow involving several actors and approval levels. These projects can be grouped together into Portfolios or other group types. The application provides aggregation of cost, duration and other metrics for projects contained within a group. Several sites including KPI dashboards, administration sites, custom reports, integration with multiple external systems.

Education

Bachelor's Degree: Visual Communications - 2008

Rodolfo Loero Arismendi Institute (Lecheria, Venezuela)

Certifications

Appian Associate Developer – 2022

Appian Corporation (Virginia, USA)

Professional English Proficiency - 2017

Wall Street Institute - School of English (Lecheria, VEN)